Gerald Romero

Software Developer

Personal details



Email address devgeraldromero@gmail.com

Phone number +639568577636

Address Sorosoro Ilaya, Batangas City, Batangas, 4200 Batangas City

Website devgeraldr.github.io

ePortfolio https://sites.google.com/ub.edu.ph/geraldromero2002289/home

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/gerald-romero-732424279

Profile

Studied at the University of Batangas majoring in Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. Have slight but solid work experience as a freelance web developer and an IT support specialist intern. Has built a good amount of personal projects (see personal website and ePortfolio for reference).

Education

2020 - 2024 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

University of Batangas, Batangas City

Thesis - ChatNB: An Al Driven Chatbot Utilizing Natural Language Processing

to facilitate conversation with Notable Batangueños.

- Best in Thesis

Experience

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023 Web developer (Freelance)

Protected Area Management Board of Mts. Palay-Palay/Mataas Na

Gulod

PL, Sapang I, Ternate, Cavite

July 2023 - September 2023 IT Support Specialist

TaskUs

L/G Xentro Mall Extension, Diversion Road, Batangas City

Skills

Web Development with React JS, Firebase, NoSQL, MySQL, Node JS, and Tailwind CSS. Mobile Development with JavaScript, React Native, Firebase, NoSQL, and Tailwind CSS. Ability to use Git and GitHub.